{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Statements: Some actors are singers. All the singers are dancers.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nSome actors are dancers.\nNo singer is actor.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "A", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: All the harmoniums are instruments. All the instruments are flutes.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nAll the flutes are instruments.\nAll the harmoniums are flutes.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: Some mangoes are yellow. Some tixo are mangoes.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nSome mangoes are green.\nTixo is a yellow.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: Some ants are parrots. All the parrots are apples.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nAll the apples are parrots.\nSome ants are apples.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: Some papers are pens. All the pencils are pens.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nSome pens are pencils.\nSome pens are papers.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "E", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: All the actors are girls. All the girls are beautiful.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nAll the actors are beautiful.\nSome girls are actors.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "E", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: All the windows are doors. No door is a wall.\r\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nSome windows are walls.\nNo wall is a door.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: All cups are books. All books are shirts.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nSome cups are not shirts.\nSome shirts are cups.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: Some cows are crows. Some crows are elephants.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nSome cows are elephants.\nAll crows are elephants.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: All the pencils are pens. All the pens are inks.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nAll the pencils are inks.\nSome inks are pencils.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "E", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: Some dogs are bats. Some bats are cats.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nSome dogs are cats.\nSome cats are dogs.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: All the trucks are flies. Some scooters are flies.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nAll the trucks are scooters.\nSome scooters are trucks.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "D", "explanation": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows."}, {"question": "Statements: All buildings are chalks. No chalk is toffee.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nNo building is toffee\nAll chalks are buildings.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "A", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Statements: All cars are cats. All fans are cats.\n\n\nConclusions:\n\nAll cars are fans.\nSome fans are cars.", "opta": "Only (1) conclusion follows", "optb": "Only (2) conclusion follows", "optc": "Either (1) or (2) follows", "optd": "Neither (1) nor (2) follows", "opte": "Both (1) and (2) follow", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}]]}